

CONTACT

- **(%)** +971 50 704 6133
- 🖾 clavitafernandes03@gmail.com
- clavitafernandes.vercel.app
- (©) clavi.osa

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Ai ×××××







PERSONAL SKILLS

- + Curious
- Adaptable
- Multitasking
- + Resourceful
- Team-oriented

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Mass Media

Sophia College, Mumbai 2020 - 2023

Secondary Education Wilson College, Mumbai 2018-2020

Primary Education Nazareth School, Mumbai May 2018

CLAVITA FERNANDES

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm Clavita, a 21-year-old self taught artist based in Dubai. I'm a Visual Storyteller, crafting designs that help Brands find their visual Identity - be it through Illustration, Branding or Logo. Off duty, a mix media artist/animator sharing & exploring art trends on instagram.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer
Oct 2023 - Present

Ti22 Films

- Designed social media posts for brands like Dubai One's DXB Today, Instaglam, Yspot.
- Designed stage backdrop for Yspot's Ignite event held at Sharjah University.
- Created animated graphics for Arva
 Ahmed's Ditch the silver YouTube Channel.

Graphic Design Intern

May 2023 - Aug 2023

Altois

- Designed logo for iMUSE, (makeup academy by celebrity artist Neha Mahajan).
- Made creative Ads for Daniel Bauer Makeup Academy.

Graphic Design Intern

May 2022 - Jul 2022

SoCheers

- Designed social media posts for brands like Amazon Mini TV, Meemee, MenMoms.
- Designed digital hoardings for Amazon Modern love campaign.

NOTABLE COLLEGE ROLES

Senior Executive

Jul 2022 - Feb 2023

Art & Design Club

• Ideated & organized events, hosted live sessions, and managed social media.

Team Creatives Coordinator

Aug 2022 - Sep 2022

Kaleidoscope Annual Festival

 Ideated fest theme, Designed event brochure, social media posts, and website.

Senior Designer

April 2021 - April 2022

Beyond Margins

 Designed website & social media creatives, Illustrated cover, & designed annual brochure 2022.